Finding Aid for Ward Family Papers 1860-1964
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Maps
  Manuscript and printed maps relating to the family's lumbering and land holdings in the northern Lower Peninsula of Michigan (including land ownership maps and maps of logging operations), Orchard Lake, Michigan (including maps of roads and subdivisions), Humboldt and Del Norte Counties, California, the Kanawha Valley of West Virginia, and Vancouver Island, British Columbia
  - British Columbia, 5 maps (Map-case 1, Folder 3)
    (published maps, 1907 and 1929, and blueprint maps, undated and 1925 of Ward lands on Vancouver Island; and blueprint map, 1900s?, of land along Fraser River, British Columbia)
  - West Virginia, 2 maps (Map-case 1, Folder 3)
    (published map, 1880s?, of Kanawha Valley, West Virginia; and manuscript plat, undated, of Ward land)
  - California, 19 maps (Map-case 1, Folder 4)
    (maps of Ward lands in Humboldt and Del Norte Counties, including published county maps, 1901-1935, and printed and blueprint maps, 1929-1952, of Ward and other land holdings and logging operations; also blueprint plat of land in Montecito, 1904)
  - Michigan
    - Northern Lower Peninsula
      - David Ward estate land holdings 1914-1925, undated, 13 maps (Map-case 1, Folder 5)
        (printed maps with annotations showing timber, tax, and sales status of estate)
      - Land ownership maps of townships 1882-1889, undated, 43 maps (Map-case 1, Folder 6)
        (manuscript Maps showing land ownership in townships in Antrim, Charlevoix, Cheboygan, Crawford, Emmet, Kalkaska, Manistee, and Otsego Counties)
      - Logging operations in Antrim and Otsego Counties 1886-1911, undated, 37 maps (Map-case 1, Folder 7)
        (manuscript maps of operations in T29N, R4 and 5W, and T30N, R5W)
    - Orchard Lake area 1922-1956, 14 maps (Map-case 1, Folder 8)
      (blueprint, manuscript, and printed maps of roads and subdivisions in West Bloomfield Lakes development)
Related Material
The Bentley Historical Library holds related material in the Palmer Family papers and Edmond DeVine papers.